https://www.thelandbetween.ca/privacy-policy/

Donate a Car
This privacy policy is intended to inform you how we use information that is collected from you on this website. Please read the privacy policy before using this website or submitting any information through this website.
Collection of Information
Personal Information
When you use our online contact forms or email, we require that you provide your name and email address so that we can respond to your specific request. We will never sell, trade or share this information with any third party. Other information you provide, such as location data for rare species sightings, will be shared only with your permission.
Cookie/Tracking Technologies
Our website may use cookie and tracking technologies to gather information about your web browser and operating system, to monitor the number and nature of visitors, and to understand how visitors are using the website. Our website may also use cookies for advanced features such as personalization. No personal information is collected via cookies and tracking technology.
Information Security
No personal information is stored on this website or is accessible through this website. Feedback submitted through the website may be monitored by our webmaster for the purposes of ensuring proper operation of the website.
Because thelandbetween.ca accepts donations through the PayPal secure payment gateway service, you are never asked to submit credit card information through this website. All credit card processing is done on the PayPal secure site. For more information about PayPal’s security measures, please click here
Email generated through links provided on this site is not secured or encrypted. Please do not provide any confidential or sensitive information via email.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this privacy policy, please see our main Contact Page.
Changes to This Policy
Changes may be made to this privacy policy without notice. However, any changes to this privacy policy will be made available on this page.
Privacy Policies on Other Websites
This privacy policy applies only to this website. If you visit other sites from links provided on this website, please ensure that you review the privacy policies posted at those websites.
Donate>
Sponsor>
Shop>
Befriend>
Shopping Cart
Upcoming Events
There are no upcoming events at this time.
Keep In Touch:
Download our FREE! mobile app to explore and tour the region:
Watch the Land Between Trailer
A visually stunning 3-part documentary series showcasing the ecological and cultural diversity and history of this region. Buy it here.
Recent News from TLB
Warming Winds of ChangeWhile warmer temperatures and increased storms are often the focus of climate change stories in the media, the often overlooked byproduct of climate … read more...
HIPPO- The Greatest Threat to BiodiversityEvery time a species goes extinct or is lost from a given area, global biodiversity is irreparably damaged and destabilized. Specific causes of losses … read more...
Clogging the Lakes- Eurasian WatermilfoilUnderstanding Eurasian Watermilfoil: What is it, How Did it Get Here, What are its Impacts, and What Can We Do to Prevent its Spread?
What is … read more...
Christmas Shopping to Support ConservationThe Land Between and our Turtle Guardians program needs your help to support conservation projects across the highlands. We have introduced new … read more...
Hiding the De-Naturing of Nature in OntarioThis month we felt it was important to share some very significant news; News that has been shared around Ontario in many circles and which affects … read more...
We are Hiring- 2 PositionsThe Land Between is looking for two positions! We are hiring a Citizen Science Outreach Coordinator, to help engage kids and communities in monitoring … read more...
Busy Beavers, Our Essential Ecosystem EngineersBeavers are easily one of the most
fascinating and unique creatures in our landscape with their impressive paddle-like tails, lush shiny fur, … read more...
Report a Species
Click the image to file your report
NewsletterSign up
First Name*Last Name*Email*
PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Home
The Organization
The Region
Stewardship
Discoveries
Tour TLB
TLB Store/Centre
Contact
News-Blog
Donate
Befriend
Sponsor
Get the FREE mobile app
Privacy Policy
The Land Between is a National Charity #805849916RR0001.
Your support helps us celebrate, conserve, and enhance this important region.
The Land Between
P.O. Box 1368
Haliburton, ON K0M 1S0
705-457-1222
info@thelandbetween.ca
We respectfully acknowledge that The Land Between is located within Williams Treaty 20 Mississauga Anishinaabeg territory and Treaty 61 Robinson-Huron treaty territory, in the traditional territory of the Anishinaabeg. The Land Between respectfully acknowledges that these First Nations are the stewards and caretakers of these lands and waters in perpetuity and that they continue to maintain this responsibility to ensure their health and integrity for generations to come.
Thank You to our Major Supporters
Search
Main Menu
The Organization
Strategic Direction, Projects and Programs
How We Operate
Honouring the Treaties
Transparency & Accountability
